My wife had plastic surgery recently. We had discussed
it, and I was against it. It was not my decision,
and ultimately I had no say. She looks weird now.
She had the fat sucked out of her face, lip fillers,
a neck lift. Other stuff I don't really get.
She gives me uncanny Valley vibes now. It freaks me
out. She is fully healed now, and she wants us to go back to
normal. Like me initiating sex. I have
done so, but not as much as I used to. And when
I do, I try and make sure there is very little light.
It's been a few months and I kind of dread having to look at her.
Obviously, she has noticed. She has been bugging me to tell her
what's up. I've tried telling her I'm just tired from work or
that I'm run down, really, anything except for the
truth. She broke down and asked me if I was having an affair.
I said that I wasn't. She asked to look at my phone.
I unlocked it for her and handed it over. I wasn't worried
about her finding anything because there is nothing to find.
She spent an hour looking through it and found nothing. She asked
me to explain why I changed. I tried explaining that.
I just wasn't that interested right now. Nothing I said
was good enough for her. She kept digging. I finally
told the truth. I wasn't harsh or brutally honest.
I just told her that her new face wasn't something I found
attractive and that I was turned off. She asked if that's why I
turn off all the lights now. I said yes.
She started crying and said that she needed time alone.
She went to stay with her sister. I have been called every name
in the book since this happened. Her sister said I'm a
piece of shit for insulting my wife's looks.
Her friends all think I'm the asshole. I tried
not to say anything. I can't force myself to find
her attractive. I still love her, but her face is just
weird now. She looks like the blue alien from the fifth
element.